THEME SONG: In the not
too distant future--
next Sunday AD-- there
was a guy named Joel,
not too different
from you or me.
He worked at Gizmonic
Institute, just another face
in a red jumpsuit, he did a
good job cleaning up the place,
but his bosses didn't like him,
so they shot him into space.
We'll send him cheesy movies,
the worst we can find.
He'll have to sit
and watch them all,
and we'll monitor his mind.
Now keep in mind,
Joel can't control
where the movies begin
or end, because he
used those special parts
to make his robot friends.
Robot Roll Call-- Cambot!
Gypsy!
Tom Servo!
Croooow!
If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes
and other science facts,
then repeat to yourself,
it's just a show, I
should really just
relax for Mystery
Science Theater 3000!
-Crow, look, here he comes!
It's Joel!
-Joel!
It's Joel, Joel, Joel!
[CHEERING]
-Hi, you guys.
How you doing?
-Oh, you know,
it's just like you
to think of us
instead of yourself.
-That's what separates
you from us measly bots.
-Thanks.
Hi, everybody.
Welcome to the
Satellite of Love.
I'm Joel Robinson
and these are--
-Oh, ya see?
He introduced himself.
What a perfectly
thoughtful thing to do.
-Oh yes, thoughtful.
-These are my robots
Tom Servo and Crow.
And I've installed in them
a protocol module that
makes them believe
everything I think, say or do
is utterly brilliant.
-Oh, and it is, Joel.
God, yes.
Oh ho ho, joy!
-Roger Penrose on his best
day isn't half as brilliant
or as charming as
you, I might add.
-Commercial sign in 15 seconds.
Of course, every
blissful second with you
is like an apple of gold, Joel.
-Ah!
-Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
-You know, I'm starting to have
second thoughts about this.
I don't know what I think.
-Oh, Joel!
I've wiped away every
bit of hesitation
I had about this project.
-Not that we'd take issue
with anything you'd think.
-Oh, no no no no.
-No no no.
-It does make it
easier to work with.
-Oh yes yes, easy as pie!
Brilliant, brilliant.
-More Evian, Mr. Miller?
-It leaves me feeling
kind of hollow.
-Wow.
How insightful of you to
find that in yourself.
-You always cut right to
the heart of things, Joel.
-Ah, yeah.
-Yeah, I'm going to
remove those modules.
-Oh, no no.
No, just, just, just, just
shut me down completely.
-Oh!
Uh, jettison me
into space, please!
-Oh, yes, disconnect
with extreme prejudice.
-You see this butt?
Kick this butt.
-We'll be right back.
All right, there's
the protocol module.
-Don't touch me.
Don't ever touch me.
-This is painful.
That-- ah!
Ungh.
[SNIFFING]
-Jeez, Joel.
Some small animal crawl
inside your jumpsuit and die?
-There's the bots
I know and love.
Uh-oh, fasten your seatbelts.
Crate & Barrel are calling.
[HUMMING_"LA_MARSEILLAISE"]
-Huh?
Oh, Joel.
A hearty hello to you and yours.
Let me just say this about
today's invention exchange--
let them eat chocolate.
-That's right, J--
That's right, Joel.
Our invention this week is based
on one's natural inclination
to bite the heads off
of chocolate bunnies.
-That's right, Frank.
That's why we've invented the
chocolate bunny guillotine.
Eliminate the guesswork in
biting the heads off bunnies.
Uh, ready, Mr. Executioner?
-Yes, my liege.
-You have stolen painted
eggs in a time of famine.
Uh, off with her head, Frank.
And no chocolate mess.
Well, poopsies?
[BOTS CRYING]
-What about the pardon
from Fanny Farmer?
-Yeah.
His only crime was
being born delicious!
-It's OK, you guys.
There, there.
It's all right.
Let's show them our invention
exchange, all right?
Our invention exchange
is called the Cartuner.
Have you ever noticed
that funnies just
aren't funny anymore?
The Cartuner takes
stodgy, ambiguous cartoons
like Mark Trail and mixes
them with stiflingly unfunny
cartoons like Blondie, puts them
together and makes them funny.
Check it out.
Well, look at this.
Huh.
Let's see what happened.
Well, OK.
And here's Dagwood, and he's
eating a giant sandwich made
out of twigs, grubs,
and a tufted titmouse.
[BOTS LAUGHING]
-That's pretty funny.
-Hey, that's funny.
-Oh, oh, oh!
Now do the Lockhorns and Cathy.
-Ooh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
-OK, Lockhorns and Cathy.
Put them in the Cartuner.
-It goes round and round.
-Yes, and it comes out here.
-Ah, let me see.
Ah-- Oh ho, hey.
Mrs. Lockhorn accidentally
crashed her car into the store
where Cathy was
trying on a swimsuit!
[LAUGHTER]
-OK.
-Hey, Joel.
Uh, let's try a panel of Bil
Keane's heartwarming Family
Circus with Gary Larson's
off-center The Far Side.
-OK, put them together, mix them
up, and we can-- and then, see,
here it is.
Huh.
-Oh, let me see there.
A dotted trail showing where
anthropomorphic jackals have
chased little Billy!
-It's a hoot!
[LAUGHING]
-Ah, the carnage!
-What do you think, sirs?
-Ahh-- my ribs.
-I don't think, I get even.
Dig this, mes amis.
Your average Joe has never seen
a film like today's experiment.
Your average person
on the street
has not even begun to
conceptualize the horror which
is your experiment
today, Mr. Joel Average.
I give to you, "Manos--
The Hands of Fate."
Served with a short, the
stirring conclusion to "Hired."
Hit the button, Frank.
-Yes.
Oh, Fluffy, you're so--
-Frank!
--Oh, Fluffy, here.
Here, you take him.
-Push the button, Frank!
-Ziggy had Garfield neutered?
Now that's funny!
[BUZZER ALARM]
-Ah, look.
"Hired 2-- Electric Boogaloo."
-A Jam Handy to the rescue.
-My Jam Handy.
-No employees were killed
during the making of this film.
-Young fellas today won't work
the way we did 11 years ago.
-Previously, on "Hired."
-Maybe not, son.
And then again, maybe they're
working harder than you think.
-I may be wonderful but
I think you're wrong.
-You were a pretty
good man when you first
started in this business.
And you probably were, but
you owe a lot of your success
to the way Harry
Carpenter worked with you
-Give 'em hell, Harry.
-He used to tell me about
the mistakes you made.
You may not have known
it, but you really
served am apprenticeship.
-Work, booze, work--
-In every business.
-Yeah, I suppose so.
-Remember how closely he
worked with you the first year?
Heh.
He used to tell me about it.
-He ripped you a
new one everyday.
-Yeah, I remember how he used to
talk to me about my prospects.
-Your prostate?
-How I was to
handle some of them.
But you know, I always
thought that that
was because he knew you so well.
Maybe he had more of a
personal interest in me.
-Nonsense.
-He hated you.
-Not Harry.
-Oh, he's having an episode.
-He worked that hard with
every man he ever hired.
-He got sent to jail for it.
-He was smart enough to
realize that he knew more
about selling cars than
any man on his sales force.
And that it took his
direction and leadership
to get the most out of his men.
-Ah!
Flying elves are back.
-And I don't believe men
have changed much since then.
-Aah!
-How about this Jimmy?
Doesn't he work?
Doesn't he get in for the
morning sales meetings?
[HICCUP]
-Oh yeah, he's always punctual.
He never misses.
But take his
prospects, for example.
-Please.
[IMITATES RIMSHOT]
-Why, I looked them
over the other day,
and it's just about the
poorest list I've ever seen.
I remember one of
the first things
that Harry drilled in to me--
-Was Harry!
-The importance of having
a good list of prospects.
-Yes?
-Then he showed me how
to go about getting it.
How to keep it up.
How to cover the list.
And how often.
-Yeah, he performed
puppet shows for me.
-I had the importance
of prospects drilled
into me from the
very first day I
-Whoa!
-Aah!
-He's evil!
-Mhm.
-Has Jimmy?
-Has Jimmy what?
-Had the importance of
prospects pounded into him
since the first day
he started to work?
-Well, I've told him
how important they are.
-Yeah, but have
you shown him how,
when and where to get them?
Have you checked
on him every day
to see that he did it right?
-Have you hugged him?
-Dad, I've got other work to do.
-Harry wasn't too busy to
make a good man out of you.
-Ah, you still got
a little-- eh-- hmm.
-Say, I think I'm beginning
to see what you mean.
-I'm beginning to sober
up and you're scaring me.
-I wonder.
-(SINGING) I wah,
wah, wah, wah, wonder.
-Say, maybe that's
the reason I haven't
had very much luck with Jimmy.
-I'm gonna dance!
-Or with Henderson, that other
fellow I hired last year.
You know, he looked
pretty good to me, too,
Dad, when I first hired him.
-Heh, who doesn't?
-Certainly would be worth a try.
-Yes, sir.
-Don't hit me!
-Come to think of it, the time
I'm spending on other things
right now might be costing me
a whole lot more than I think.
Men need leadership.
Leadership is important.
Oh, I've always known
that, Dad, but I never
thought about in connection
with my own business.
But starting Monday morning,
-Don't touch me!
-I'm gonna stir things up a bit.
I'm going to show these fellas
what leadership really means.
[HICCUP]
-And then we'll see.
-We're going to have leadership
the way my old man told me.
You, put a handkerchief
on your head!
You, swat at imaginary elves!
You, rock on the
porch all night!
-Sales are the most important
thing in this business.
-Seeing as how we're
salesmen and all.
-We're going to work
closer together than we
have in the past in
order to get more sales.
-But first, martinis!
-Well, that's all
for this meeting,
but I want to check
with each one of you
personally before you
go out this morning.
Jimmy, I'll talk with you first.
-Because you've got
the most problems.
-The meeting's adjourned.
Jimmy, from what you say,
I'd put these two away
for two weeks.
-Whack 'em.
Whack 'em good.
-Your time is too valuable to
be spending on them right now.
-Yeah, mhm.
-And then I'd take these
four in this order.
-Uh, boss, will you help
me with my soapbox racer?
-It'll save you time
in covering them.
Now have you got any others
up in this end of town
when you get up there?
-Uh, no sir.
I don't believe I have.
-All right.
-Here's a lollipop, Jimmy.
-I'll give you the names
of three Chevrolet owners
who live up that way.
-Crush 'em.
-And all three of them
should be about ready to buy.
-Meanwhile, Eliot Ness
and his Untouchables
head for a speakeasy in Berwin.
[GASPS]
-Sintar gets the most sales
because he's a shape shifter.
-Harry, I don't think you
drove quite far enough
with that prospect before
you let him take the wheel.
-Yes Mr. Warren, but
he bought the car.
-I know, I know,
but I'm speaking
about your demonstrations
in general.
-But he bought the flippin' car!
-You like to turn the
wheel over to your prospect
pretty early in the
demonstration ride.
-I know, but--
-Now, you know, of course
that when you drive first,
-Yeah, but--
-The prospect almost invariably
drives back over the same route
that you took.
-Yeah, but he bought the car!
-And if you'd driven on
to that rough stretch
up on Summit
Avenue, you wouldn't
have to direct
him over it later.
-He bought the car.
-That'll give you a chance to
have him keep his mind more
on the car than on the road.
-Uh, you got a
nice office, boss.
-It's usually best to--
I'll go along with you again
this morning, Jimmy, on
these first two calls.
-Gee, that'll be
swell, Mr. Warren.
I'll sure appreciate your help.
I always learn something
too, when we go out together.
-Yeah, maybe I can kiss your
butt on the way out, hmm?
How about that?
Heh?
He he.
-Uh, just gotta push my
family out of the way.
I kinda live out
of my car, if you
know what I mean, there, just--
-So, that's when I got into
commemorative spoon collecting.
You?
-Why don't you punch it, Jimmy.
I wanna be in Tijuana by
8 o'clock or you're fired.
-Oh, they're meeting
with Floyd the Barber.
-(IMITATING FLOYD) Oh, oh, the
car is so wonderful, oh, oh!
-Now listen, I said
no you two yesterday.
-But ma'am, do you
know that Chevrolet
has a wonderful
plan for your life?
-Why'd you bring the greasy guy?
-Better see them again tomorrow.
And be sure to have Mrs. Beckham
into the showroom tonight
with her husband.
-OK, I'll sure do it.
Thanks again for your
help, Mr. Warren.
-Uh, may I call you?
I'd like to see
ya again sometime.
-Are you now, or have you
ever been, a Ford owner?
-I wouldn't buy a car from
you if you were the last man
on Earth, you sorry sack of--
-That's where your truck
data book comes in.
-Drug data?
-You'll find the information you
want on that special equipment
right back here.
-Uh, somewheres.
-Now, show this information
to your prospect, too.
Just don't keep glancing at it
and then telling them about it.
Let them read it.
Very often, the printed word is
a big help in closing the sale.
-Oh, look, it's
salesman-parent conferences.
-Well, my life is a hollow lie.
-Just too many of them
on hand now, George.
That's the reason
we couldn't afford
to offer a higher appraisal.
-Yeah, I can see your
side of the picture.
-Yes, but there's a
good side too, George.
For example, right now we
haven't a single '39 Plymouth
four-door on the lot.
And that means we can
afford to make somebody
a pretty good offer.
-Say, I've got a prospect
downtown with one of those.
-Not too hot, but I was
going to get too him
again in the next few days.
-Fine, get him in here today.
And I'm sure we can make
them an offer that'll
close a deal for you.
Besides, we can use--
[GASPS]
-Mr. Milton, you can depend
on what our Mr. Hill here
has just told you.
And I'll give you my
own personal word,
too, that if you have any
trouble along that line,
we'll make it good.
[SNICKERING]
-Well, I don't know.
The last two cars I bought,
when they had trouble,
it was always my
fault, never the car's.
-We want you to be
just as satisfied
with your new Chevrolet
next year, Mr. Milton,
as you will be next week.
-That's exactly right.
-Just buy the car!
-We couldn't have afforded to
make the investment we have
here unless we gave the
kind of satisfaction that
make our customers come
back to us year after year.
We want you to be a regular
customer, too, Mr. Milton.
In fact, we hope you'll buy
your next ten cars from us.
-Ten cars?
-That's why we'll give
you the kind of service
it takes on this one to bring
you back for the next one.
And the next, and
the next, so on.
You see, that's the only
way we can hope to--
-How can I keep
this from Gladys?
-Adlai Stevenson buys a car.
-Good salesman.
-Bad salesman.
-(IMITATES JIMMY DURANTE)
Inka dinka do, ha ha ha ha ha!
-Now, if you want to
see your daughter again,
you'll do what I--
-And now let us pray.
Lord!
-Huh?
-You could hurt me?
-(ANGRILY) Would you sign it?
Just sign it!
Sign it!
-Well, can I keep the pen?
-I was kidding.
I was going to sign when I
walked in here, ha, you nuts.
-Christy ahead at the break,
Dunn and Stewart close behind.
-Huh?
-Believe me, leadership pays.
-Is he talking to us?
-Mhm.
-Yeah.
-First, hire good men.
-Make sure they're clean.
-Then see that they're well
trained on their own product
and on competitive products.
Second,
-Check their teeth.
-Be sure they have
all the equipment
and selling helps they need
and know how to use them.
-Fifth--
-Third,
-Oh, right, third.
-Help them plan
their work to make
the most effective
use of their time.
Fourth,
-Live at home until you're 40.
-Stay in close touch
with every man.
Know what each one is doing.
Work with them.
-Name names.
-And fifth, keep up
their enthusiasm.
-En-too-zee-az-um.
-Encourage every man every day.
-Give 'em backrubs.
-And never forget,
-I love you.
-As I did, that people
who represent you--
-It's Dr. Giggles!
-Need your help.
-Goodnight.
Stay pink, soft and oily.
-(SINGING) We're hired!
-Hired!
-Yes, it's Manos,
the Hands of Fate.
-You know, this is the slowest
car chase scene I've ever seen.
-Like father, like son.
Think about it, won't you?
-This is where you
get out, honey.
-We're almost there, honey.
Just a little while longer
and your vacation starts.
-I've been cold, Mother.
-Visit beautiful ground zero.
-Hey, look.
Poodle bites, poodle chews.
-(IN CHILD'S VOICE) His
heartbeat's irregular.
-We should be pretty
close right now.
The agent said it was about
12 miles from Highway 10
and that was Highway
10 back there.
-But you know, we
should've asked
for better directions
at the last gas station.
-Listen, I've never
gotten us lost before.
-Have I?
Honey?
-Mommy, I'm cold.
-(IN CHILD'S VOICE)My core
temperature's dropped.
-OK, Debbie.
I'll put the top up.
-Nevermind, Mike.
Debbie can come
up sit between us.
-You can have the top up
or a birthday present.
It's your choice, honey.
-Ah, what do you
want, a hug next?
Jeez, kids.
-Cousin Itt!
[IMITATES COUSIN ITT SOUNDS]
-Why don't we sing a song
to help pass the time?
-(IN CHILD'S VOICE)Let's sing
something from Pearl Jam.
-(SINGING) Row,
row, row your boat.
Gently down the steam
-Row, row, row your boat-- come
on, sing, sing, sing, damn it,
sing!
Row, row, row your
boat, that's it, sing!
Down the stream, yes!
Row--
-(SINGING AS A DOG)
Ruff, ruff, rowr ra rowr
-Gently down the stream--
[IMITATING DOG PANTING]
-Merrily, merrily,
merrily, merrily--
-Maryland, Maryland--
-Our Man From UNCLE
will return after this.
-Slug bug!
[JOEL PUNCHES CROW]
-Ow!
Jeez.
-Well, you know, "Manos."
-Right, right not
in so many words.
-You know, "Manos."
-Oh, yeah.
I hear ya.
-Tonight, Manos gets caught in
a deadly game of cat and mouse.
[POLICE SIREN]
-Ah, sorry, but you're not
filming "Manos-- Hands of Fate"
in our town.
-Mm-mm.
-Maybe it's a hot poodle.
-(IRISH ACCENT) All right,
nothing to see here,
show's over.
I love that one.
-Cover me, Ron.
Check this out.
-You have any idea how you
were framing back there?
-All right, Mister.
I see you have a
tail light problem.
No excuse.
Running late, first vacation,
kid getting tired-- too bad.
[INAUDIBLE]
-Can't you give us a break?
-This is just one guy talking.
Just one guy.
-All right.
-Sure do appreciate it.
We are running kind of late.
-Just one guy.
-If you're running late, you
should've started earlier.
-Is it Jeffrey Zaslow?
-Anyhow, no tail light.
Have it fixed.
-Thank you, officer.
-Thank God he didn't
search the trunk, honey.
-You know, that was just one
guy doing all those voices.
I can't believe it.
-So, what are we, about
half hour into this movie?
-No, I'm afraid not.
It's more like a minute.
-No.
-Yeah.
-Huh.
-If you lived here,
you'd be home by now.
-Look, pigs, lies and videotape.
-Joel, this is going to
turn into a snuff film.
-Oh, the Mads wouldn't do
this, this is not a snuff film,
I guarantee it.
-Hey look, them Blue
Kentucky Hills of Tennessee.
-All right, a little Manos,
taking us up to news time here.
Manos--
-Honey, please.
Not while I'm driving!
-Valley Loo-gee?
-Ugh.
-Luge.
K. What about the Valley Lodge??
-Now, just ten miles--
-No!
Now they're going
back the other way!
-Just a few minutes, now.
-Hey, let's just
pretend we're watching
"Trip To Bountiful," hmm?
-Guess they picked up
Shirley Bassey hitch hiking.
-In summary, "Manos--
the Hands of Fate."
-"Manos-- the Hands of Fate."
-Manos.
Ooh.
-Oh, honey.
-What's gotten into you?
-You.
-Oh, sure, they dissolve
to the same scene.
See?
-Anybody have any Dramamine?
-(SINGING) It's Robin
Stone, the Love Machine.
-Hey!
Manos takes it up a notch.
-Uh, Mr. Unser,
we're ready for ya.
Mr. Unser?
-Go, Speed Racer.
-So, Worcestershire, honey?
[GULP SOUNDS]
[GASP]
-Yes, it's Hawaiian Tropic,
for that savage buzz.
-Oh, you're getting
cuter and funnier
and I'm liking
you more and more.
-So, ahem, hmm, uh-- what do you
want to talk about n-- Mmf, mm.
-Yuck, it sounds
like Jerry Reed, ugh!
[IMITATES CAR HORN]
-Way to go, Steve!
-Ugh.
Tastes like cherry Robitussin.
-I wonder where they're going.
-Man, like, there's
nothing up that road.
-Well, back at it.
Break's over.
-You are the driver.
What would you do if
this happened to you?
Manos.
-Hmm.
Gotta keep an eye on my widow's
peak, in the mirror there.
-Boy, this is a
taut thriller, huh?
-"Manos-- the Hands of Fate."
-Mhm.
-Manos.
-What?
It-- This isn't Wacker Drive,
we're nowhere near Chicago.
-Now, look.
The sign pointed this way.
-Mike, let's go back
to the crossroads--
-Hey, dialogue.
-And ask those kids we saw.
-OK, OK.
But I know we can't be wrong.
Look, the sign pointed this way!
-The sign pointed this way!
Admit I'm right!
-Hm.
-So, once again, in
case you forgot--
"Manos-- the Hands of Fate."
-Sure is a quiet ride.
Hey, Mister.
Get those hands at 10
o'clock at 2 o'clock, now.
-Pretty soon, now,
I'm guessing we'll
find "Manos-- The
Hands of Fate."
-Look, can we drop
off Tim Weisberg, now?
-And now, "Herbie Manos--
the Hands of Fate."
-"Manos!"
-"The Hands of Fate"?
-Yes.
-Mhm.
-Hoomph.
Good thing they got a roll bar.
-(IRISH ACCENT) All
right, shove over, kid.
-Have to chase you kids.
-Oh, sheesh.
Holy cow, man.
You'd think we're
doing something wrong.
-No, you got it all wrong.
Love should be
musty and hurtful.
-Whatever it is
you're not doing,
go don't do it somewhere else.
-Why don't you guys
leave us alone?
-Will I have a bad rep?
-Come on, now.
No wisecracks.
-No more brittle bons mots.
-OK.
-Get going.
Get going.
-That means us.
-Well, you don't
have to go away mad.
-Well, kids, it's
time for us to go
on our motor tour of the
southwestern states featuring
many sites of
historical interest.
-Oh, this is really nice!
Hey, look, there's a field.
And another field.
-Oh, yes.
It's very scenic.
It's just like a scene
from-- (STARTS TO BREAK DOWN)
"Manos-- the Hands of Fate."
[CRYING]
-You said Manos!
-Uh, Tom you're
breaking character.
-Well, I know but you're
using footage from the film.
It makes me want to
blow my brains out!
-Uh, that's nice, dear.
Look, there are many other
points of scenic enjoyment
to be viewed with
bemused interest.
Why there's the ma--
corn palace over there.
[GYPSY IMITATING POLICE SIREN]
-Oh, my.
It is the man.
I hope we don't get
carted to the big house.
-My, my, my.
What do we have here?
[SPITS]
[CLANG]
-Ick.
Look-y like we got us
some Yankee troublemakers.
I'm-a gonna have
to bring you in.
-Uh, aren't you gonna
read us our rights?
-He wants me to
read him his rights.
Wah ha ha ha ha!
-Hey, listen, man.
We don't have to take any--
-(WHISPERING) Crow.
Crow, look.
-Oh, je-- geeze, Cambot!
You were supposed to stop the
footage on the blue screen
when Gypsy pulled us over!
How are we supposed to do a
sketch when we have to watch--
(STARTS WHIMPERING) Ma-
Manos the Hands of Fate??
[CRYING]
-Oh, god.
-We're never gonna make it!
This is a bug hunt, man!
A bug hunt!
-Game over, man!
Game over!
-Listen, you guys, come on.
Shh.
Hey, stay frosty.
Come on, we survived "Monster
A-Go-Go," we can survive this.
-Well!
My big scene-- ruined!
I've never seen such
unprofessionalism.
-Uh, guys, uh, I know this is
not normal procedure for me
to do this, but, uh--
DR. FORRESTER
(OFFSCREEN): Frank?
I'm out of the shower!
I need you to towel me off.
-Uh, coming, sir!
Uh, I just wanted to
say how really sorry
I am about "Manos--
the Hands of Fate."
I mean, I know it's our job
to send you really bad movies,
but this time even I have to
admit-- we really went too far.
I'm really sorry.
Now-- now, now, now that,
that sketch you were doing,
that was really funny.
N- now, go on.
Continue on with that.
Go on, go on.
[BOTS WHIMPERING]
-(STUTTERING) Na na Now,
come on, Crow, Servo.
I, I-- I told you
to keep playing.
Now come on.
Uh, uh, play!
-(DISTRAUGHT) Oh, Daddy!
-Oh, look, haven't you
done enough damage already?
Unfortunately,
we'll be right back.
-"Manos-- the Hands of Fate."
-Mhm. "Manos--
the Hands of Fate"
was filmed on location
in a vacant lot.
-Still holding.
Adorn.
-Where did this place come from?
Wasn't here a few minutes ago.
-I don't care.
Let's see if we can
get some directions.
-Maybe it's Brigadoon.
-There's someone at the door.
-The hell?
-Uh, you're rolling.
Mister--
-You know, every
frame of this movie
looks like someone's
last known photograph.
-On second thought, let's
go back and ask him.
I'm lost.
-Shot on location in
Spooner, Wisconsin.
-Uh, are you part of
the movie we're in?
-I wet 'em!
-Guy looks like a
chainsaw sculpture.
-Tom Cruise is Dr. John.
-He seems tame enough.
-Hey, you're nothin'
special, either, you guys.
-Um, could somebody
break the ice, please?
-Well, this does look inviting.
-Uh-- honey.
Why don't you talk
to the hairy man?
You're good with people.
There's a good girl.
-Uh, you two stay
with the nice man.
I'm going to go find a Ramada.
-OK, we brought the kid.
Now give us the negatives.
-Oo, buh, I don't feel so good.
Bluh.
-I am Torgo.
I take care of the place
while the Master is away.
-The Master?
Bobby Fischer?
-How proud your parents must be.
-But the child.
I'm not sure the
Master would approve.
Or the dog.
The Master doesn't
like children.
-Hey, he's W.C. Fields.
-We only want to know
where Valley Lodge is.
-Which way do we go?
-There is no place
like that around here.
[BELCHES]
-Oh, there, better.
Ahem.
Ahh.
-Mike, I'm scared.
-Of what?
-It's getting dark.
-Sure, he is from
the edge of Hell.
-Which way is out of here?
-Look, lady, I have
that effect on people,
but I'm not a bad guy.
-There is no way out here.
It will be dark soon.
There is no way out of here.
-It'll be dark soon.
-No way out?
-Well, you know, we, we could
spend the night here and then
tomorrow--
-I-I don't want to
spend the night here.
I don't like the
look of the place.
-Well, it seems we
have no alternative.
Well, how about it, Torgo?
Can we spend the night here?
-Look, we got a convention
in town, I'm sorry.
-I don't know what
else we can do.
-Mike, I don't
want to stay here.
-A-and the Master
wouldn't approve.
-Don't worry about it.
We're here now, and I'm sure
the master won't throw us out.
Well?
How about it, Torgo?
-I don't want to
stay, let's leave.
-The guy buys right into
the whole Master thing.
-I don't know about it.
I just don't know.
-I'll have to run it
by my sales manager.
-And the negotiations
continued into the night.
-Ambiguity is scary.
-Boy, I'm torn.
Torgo?
My wife?
Hmmm.
-What is this, Final Jeopardy?
-Now, look.
I've got some beans
going back there, I--
-The rod of my
staff discomfort me.
-He's the guy you used to know
who works at a Kinney's Shoes
and won't leave you alone.
-Man, pillow pants.
-You can vacation
with Torgo but don't
bring your American
Express card.
-Very well.
The Master will
be very disturbed.
-Here, go chat with the
Master, honey, there.
-Heh, heh, kids.
You got family, Torgo?
-I'll get the luggage.
-Uhh-- that's not how you
wear your Depends, Torgo.
-Been hittin' the
Thighmaster, Torgo?
-Torgo, we'll stay tonight
and then tomorrow--
-You must leave.
You cannot stay.
The Master would
not, uh, approve.
-Oh, what does the
Master approve?
-Uh.
Heh.
Uh, the door's over
that way, Torgo.
-I'm losing it.
Left-- oh, there I go,
I'm going left, help.
I'm-- oh, ohh.
-It's like having Joe
Cocker as your bellhop.
-Uh, careful, honey, Torgo's
been marking his territory.
-Oh, look, honey.
Torgo has a little
altar to Ba'al.
-Looks like they had a little
problem with the last fire
there.
Yule log got out of hand.
-See, you're feeling
better already.
-Rolling in filth
will do that for you.
-Look at this.
-What the--?
What-- oh.
-The haunting "Torgo Theme."
-Well, it's almost
as if you don't
want him to carry
your luggage, dear.
-Hey, Torgo, gotta match?
Heh, just kidding.
-I swear I know that guy.
-Heh, it's fun.
Heh, fun.
-Never seen her so happy, dear.
-I'm bemused by this
plucky painting.
-It's a, uh, Frank Frazetta
of a, uh, of Frank Zappa.
-I'm thinking of having that
tattooed on my face, dearest.
-Tonight, on "Night Gallery."
-OK, so, should we
head down to the bar?
-Must be the Master, himself.
-Yeah, he just exudes
authority, he does.
MARGARET (OFFSCREEN):
Oh, Mike, I'm scared.
He has the meanest look.
-Yeah, and it won't go
with your sofa, either.
MIKE (OFFSCREEN): I'd hate
to run up on him in the dark,
or even in the light,
for that matter.
-Honey, uh, should we
be in a cut away here?
-Um-- next slide, please.
Next slide.
-Hey, look at those lamprey
eels on the wall back there.
-I left a piece of chewed
gum on your pillow.
-Oh, that's the playful
side of Torgo, right there.
He has fun.
-He's the clown that makes the
dark side fun. (SINGING) Torgo.
-Uh, the dog is
sharp again, Mommy.
See?
That must be your Master.
Where did you say he was?
-He's in Houston this week.
-But he is with us always.
No matter where we
go, he is with us.
-You know, I bet the Master
and I would really get along.
I'd like to think that.
-What?
-No matter where he goes?
What does that mean?
And that dog.
It's the most vicious-looking
animal I've ever seen.
-Well, I, hope he goes
where the Master goes.
-There is nothing
to fear, madam.
The Master likes you.
Nothing will happen to you.
He likes you.
-Likes me?
I thought you said he was dead.
-Honey!
You're embarrassing Torgo.
-Dead?
No, madam, not dead
the way you know it.
-Uh, look, it's
kinda complicated.
But I can show you to your room.
-Not dead the way you know it.
He is with us always.
-Makes sense to me, honey.
What's your problem?
-Mike, I don't like this.
-Nothing to worry about.
It's only your imagination.
-Can Scruffy eat
this silverfish?
-Well, then.
So, Master, uh, pay
ya pretty well, huh?
-Man, that poor kid.
-Mhm.
-Gee.
-I think that it's best that I
show you to the bedrooms now.
-Oh, you'd like
that, wouldn't you?
-Hmm.
Nice guy.
[HOWLING]
-Oh my God!
Mike, what was that?
-It's Howlin' Wolf.
(SINGING) Gonna
womp that wang dang
doodle all night long.
[HOWLING]
-Hey, look, I know you're
an evil hell beast,
but could you hold it down?
It's after nine and we got kids!
-I'll go check this out.
Haha!
Fifi to the rescue!
[BARKING]
-That's it.
Mix it up, Fifi.
Go.
Go neck, Fifi.
Neck.
-What happened?
I heard--
-Stay here.
Get back into the house.
-Someone left a cake
out in the rain.
-Sounds like Gene
Krupa's out here.
-OK, let's see here.
Wet naps, flashlight,
revolver, good.
-Finally, my chance to
get rid of that damn dog.
-Ugh, look at the pile he left.
-Petrified poodle.
-Uh, good news honey.
We can get that Rottweiler.
-Get back in the house, damn it!
-My God, Mike.
What happened?
-He's dead.
Peppy's been killed.
[GASPS]
-But who's Peppy?
-Get in the house, honey.
-Mike, what kind
of place is this?
My God, what kind
-I'll take care of everything.
Honey, get back in the house.
-Oh, and don't slam-- bang!
--the screen door.
-Come on, fling her.
Side arm, go for distance, woo!
Sorry, Fluffy.
-Well, I don't know
what she got into,
but she's been out
cold for hour-- oh.
-Uh, hi, dear the dog's dea--
oh, that came out all wrong.
-Mike.
Oh, Mike, what could've done it?
-Ozzy Osbourne?
-What are you guys
talking about?
Where's my dog?
-Honey, it was probably
some animal from the desert.
This place must be full of them.
-Are you talk--
talking about my dog?
Where's my dog?
-Peppy?
-Yeah, well, listen,
you've never had a dog.
Never.
I want you to stop this
foolishness about a dog!
-Mike, I want to
leave this place.
Now!
-Aw, come on.
We haven't seen the pool yet.
-Where the hell
is that caretaker?
Torgo!
-No dog, honey.
Never.
No dog.
-Man, I can't help but
wonder what this cast
party was like when
they shot this.
-I got your magic fingers going.
-Did you want me?
-We're leaving.
Would you mind putting the
luggage back in the car?
-Look, sir, could you do it?
-As you wish.
-Right now.
Fast, damn it, fast!
-Yeah, here I go.
Vrooom!
[ENGINE REVVING]
-Sounds like he's got a
humpback whale under the hood.
-When is this guy going
to start demonstrating
some simple competence?
Jeez.
-What is he expecting,
a big on/off switch?
-Wish that Master
fellow was here.
He could fix it.
-Uh, I like your dress.
I could introduce
you to the Master.
My name actually is Roger.
-Van Gogh's
self-portrait, really.
-Well, I've got to get going.
-We got some poodle meat
in the freezer for ya.
-I'll be glad to leave.
I've had all of
this place I want.
-Uh, fill out your comment card.
-The Master wants you.
-Wants me?
What kind of talk is that?
-Why, it's oily, sleazy talk.
-He wants you for his wife.
He loves beautiful women.
-And he likes to wear mittens.
-Look, I may have
spoken out of turn.
Ah.
-You're coming on a
little strong, Torgo.
-She's just not into
dating right now.
-Hmm, now some highlights
right here would look good.
I think bangs and an off
the shoulder look for you.
-When carnies flirt.
-Torgo, you're
coming dangerously
close to crossing the line.
-Kind of a clumsy pass there.
-(SINGING) I want a
lover with a slow hand.
-You led me on.
You gave me mixed signals.
-Well, I did it.
I don't regret it.
Here's the toast you ordered.
Jam?
-Don't you ever try that again!
You-- beast!
-I'm just as God made me, ma'am.
-But he can't have you.
I want you!
-Stop that talk this
instant, you hear?!
-He wants you, but
he can't have you.
-Mike!
Mike!
-Hey, why don't you
visit with Torgo a while?
I'll be right in there, dear!
-(MUTTERING) Ugh, driving
halfway over hell in Texas.
Stupid brat kid and rat
dog, I'm glad he's dead.
[ENGINE REVVING]
-Turn it off.
Turn it off!
-God, I look like Jack Klugman.
-Where in the world could he be?
Mike!
-I might have gone out with you,
but you were just too pushy.
-Let me out of here.
Let me out of here now!
Do you hear?
Now!
-Look, lady, I got the
moves of a wallaby.
-Forgive me, madam.
-Ho ho, it's Senator Packwood.
-I meant no harm.
-She's a Breck girl.
-Forgive you?
Just wait'll I tell my husband!
-Well, I must go cut
off my left ear now.
-I meant no harm,
madam, I'll protect you.
-Because there's some
weird people around here.
-Very well.
I won't tell my husband.
Now let me out.
-And I have my answer.
I'm walking on air.
-Oh, I'm beat.
I'm hittin' the stain.
-Hey, Maggie, the
damn car won't start.
-Yeah, that's a
real bitch, Daddy.
-Margaret?
-Damn car won't start.
-Well, that really fixes things.
What are we gonna do now?
-I don't know.
And I couldn't find anything
wrong with it, either.
Hey, Torgo.
Where's the phone?
-Oh, these two.
Yes, Alexander Graham Bell.
You know, telephone?
-Don't patronize me, sir.
-There is none, sir.
The Master doesn't approve
of, uh-- such-- eh, devices.
-Th-- then where is
the nearest phone?
The nearest phone is
at the crossroads.
[HUMS_"CROSSROADS"_]
-And that's 10 miles.
-10 miles?
Might as well be 10,000 miles.
-Easy, honey.
It won't help to get mad.
-Get Glad!
-The Master won't mind
you staying tonight.
-He has no choice.
We can't leave, we
can't walk out of here,
and the damn car won't start.
-I'll just bring the
bags back to the room.
-You know, uh, Torgo wobbles,
but he won't fall down.
-You know, he can fill out
jodhpurs like regular pants.
-Mommy, didn't I have a poodle?
-You never had a poodle!
-Oh! [FAKE CRYING]
-Sinister isn't
descriptive enough.
-Honey, we'll leave
in the morning
and soon this place
will be forgotten.
-Forgotten?
I'll never forget.
-I'll always have Torgo!
-Peppy's gone.
I just hope Debbie
will understand.
-She'll understand.
She's my baby.
She'll understand.
-Play what?
Debbie's outta here!
-I hope so, darling.
I sure hope so.
-She's my baby.
She'll understand.
-Didn't he just say that?
-Say, where is she?
-Oh my god!
Michael!
Don't get rawed out.
She's probably
playing hide and seek.
-Rawed out?
-OK, Debbie.
We see you.
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
-Maybe she slipped
into one of the rooms.
-Debbie?
-Debbie!
-Ah.
After a thorough search
of the first room.
-Debbie!
-Torgo, have you seen Debbie?
-No.
-She's gone.
Help us find her.
-Could you page her for us?
-She couldn't have gone outside.
The door is bolted.
-For God's sake, don't panic.
She's got to be in here.
-Maybe she tunnelled out.
-Is there another
exit to the outside?
-In the kitchen.
-Don't touch the oatmeal
cookies in there.
-That door's bolted, too!
-We gotta go.
-These two!
-She's got to be outside.
-All right, we'll
look outside for her.
-Ohh.
Ohh.
Yeah!
Woo!
I owe ya one, buddy.
-Pretty lame monster in
this movie today, ah?
-Yeah-heh.
Wow.
Typical.
What monster?
-You know, Torgo.
Real lame monster?
-Torgo's a monster?
What do you think, Tom?
-Well, uhh-- think
that, uh, sure.
Yeah.
Seems to me that-- yeah.
Uh, exaggerated
physical attribute--
in this case, the knees--
used to induce, umm-- terror.
Yeah, I guess he's a monster.
Yeah.
-Oh, now I really
hate this movie!
How long did that decision
take the director?
A tenth of a second?
Big knees!
Good!
Let's go with it!
-Yeah, you're right.
I mean, there's got be a ton
of other exaggerated physical
attributes that'd be
a whole lot scarier.
Like if I wanted
to scare people,
I'd have really huge forearms.
-Well, ya-- kinda do.
What I'd do, see, get this--
I'd have one big droopy pinky.
[GASPS]
-And I'd drag it
behind me, hahaha!
-Hey, what if you had
one buttcheek that
was way bigger
than the other one?
-Hoo!
-Ugh!
-My head, a canker.
-A big, giant canker.
Nothing but.
-I'd have one really
big flared nostril.
And inside would be lots
of red, matted hair.
-I'd have an ear that would
cover me like a shroud.
And a thumb the size
of a juggling pin.
-Yah!
-But not on my hand.
-Nipples-- many
sizes, many shapes.
Some on my back.
-A tongue the size
of a sleeping bag.
And my fingers would
fold the other way.
Think about it.
-On my face, everything
normal except no nose.
-Nothing?
-Nope, not even holes.
Think how disturbing
that would be.
Aah!
-My intestines on
top of my head!
-No!
-Where I'd have to
keep them greased.
-I'd remove my skin, re-stitch
it, and wear it as a cardigan.
-I would have a dewlap.
-Monster.
I just don't see how you
can call Torgo a monster.
-But he is!
He is a monster!
-No, he isn't.
-He 's a monster.
-Nuh uh.
Ha ha, cut it out.
Ha ha.
Cut it out!
[LAUGHING]
[BUZZER ALARM]
-Oh no, we got movie sign!
[LAUGHING]
-Mike, I'm scared.
The animals, this desert--
-Cut it out!
[CRYING]
-What is that?
-A symbol for their love?
-Well, it's not
framed very well.
-Mm.
-There, there, honey.
We can have another daughter.
And a poodle, too.
He he, yes.
-Dear, come on.
You're soaking my
favorite golf sweater.
-Honey, when you look for
someone, what do you do?
-Debbie?
-Little Debbie?
-Debbie!
-Debbie knows it's
Prince Spaghetti night!
-Now, you be a good puppy.
-All right, freeze, Debbie!
Not another step.
Don't move!
-Mike, i-it's the dog
from the portrait.
-Stand back, Debbie!
Stand back!
-It's a devil and it's fun!
Ha!
-His name's Mephisto.
Can we keep him?
-Darling.
Baby, you could've been hurt.
-Kids worship the
darnedest things.
-But you should never
run away from us.
Debbie, don't ever
-And don't consort
with the Devil.
-Find my puppy.
-Where did you find
the new dog, baby?
-In a big place.
-In a big place?
Where, Debbie?
-The Northwest Territories.
-There was this
big, giant place.
It was so dark but I
wasn't afraid of the dark.
-Oh, she tells a
good story, huh?
-Mm.
-Yeah.
-Where is the place, Debbie?
-Over here, Daddy.
-Wait a minute, I think she
wants us to follow her, Laura.
-Ladies and gentlemen,
tonight, at the Copacabana,
Jules Podell proudly presents--
Pat Benatar and Tricia Nixon!
-Oh, Mike, it's horrible!
Let's get out of here.
-Let's go!
I'm Tom Bodett and we'll
leave a pyre on for ya.
-Ha ha, all for fun.
-Great dinner, too.
-I'm gonna find Torgo.
He's got some explaining to do.
-Hurry!
Please, hurry!
-Great hotel.
Really convenient to
the mouth of Hell.
-29 buck a night.
For what?
-They've done a
lot with the place.
-Boss, I got the
ice machine fixed.
-Daddy, I need a drink of water.
-I want her.
She's mine!
Mine!
Do you hear?
I want this one.
You have all the wives you need.
Look!
-And in a moment, the
results of that trial.
-I just wanted to know if you
could work for me Saturday.
-Oh, you pretty ones.
Let me see how good you are.
I won't need--
-He's doing "Macbeth."
-I'll have my own wife.
I won't have to
come in here to--
-It was Callahan, the big one.
He did this to me!
-You.
You're the worst.
You were his first wife.
He doesn't want you anymore.
Now even I don't want you.
-Uh, Torgo.
Don't burn any
bridges yet, buddy.
-Well, I've said my piece.
-Devil's comforter.
-So do you wanna get
some coffee or something?
-Itsy-bitsy spider
goes up the water--
-'Scuse me.
'Scuse me.
I realize this is
a little awkward.
-Oh.
-Well, his technique
has improved somewhat.
-Thank you for letting
me get this off my chest.
-Uh oh.
Ahh.
Oh.
Uh.
-Uh, let's just keep
this between you and me.
-I'm, I'm through
with all of you.
Through!
-Oh, my hernia.
-And there goes Torgo,
he's rounding the Master,
heading for the straightaway,
and there he goes!
-Oh, well, I don't know.
I guess it hasn't been
that good of a vacation.
-(SINGING) Torgo-- I just
met a fella named Torgo.
-Marilyn Quayle in "Baby Doll."
-Hmm.
Mrs. Phyllis Torgo.
Guess I kinda like it.
-Oh!
Listen, you guys.
That's it.
This is not for your eyes.
I don't care.
-What is it?
What's going on, Joel?
-Shame on you, Doctor Forrester!
Have you no sense of decency?
-What, what, is Torgo juggling?
-Joel, we can handle this.
-Ha ho, it's the latest episode
of the Taster's Choice saga.
-Showers, anyone?
-Parents, now would be a good
time to talk to your children.
-Hmm?
-Va-voom, I'm gone!
-Where is Siegfried?
-Hello, Roy!
-Hello, Siegfried!
-Hello, Roy.
-Who was looking
at Maggie the cat?
-Ooh!
Got him right in the sweet spot.
-Oh, that's a spaceship.
-It's a flashlight.
-Oh.
-Oh, my leg, my leg, oh.
Oh my, my leg.
My other leg.
Oh.
-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
-Looks like a really
cheap Robert Bly workshop.
-Man, I hit a lot
of guys, buddy,
but you really take the cake.
Heh-- tap, you're down.
-Oh, and the hell
of it is, he's never
going to get that
cashmere sweater cleaned.
-Uh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
-Oh, Torgo, no!
Not-- oh, now he's really
becoming unappealing.
Ew!
-You know, maybe Torgo should've
let him get closer to that pole
and then hit him.
-Ew.
-Oh, great.
Torgo's giving him a snuggy.
-That was "Manos--
the Hands of Fate"
on "Music Through The Night."
I'm [INAUDIBLE]
-Float!
-Ooh.
Oh, man.
I left a wake up call for 1953.
What year is it?
-Oh man, I don't
mind telling ya,
my bladder has
hit critical mass.
-Doggy go walkies?
Hmm?
Is that a good doggy?
Yes.
Good hell beast.
-He's not a morning person.
-Ohh, I get it.
-Aah.
-Oohh.
-Next week on "Manos."
-Something happens after this?
-(SINGING) So kiss
a little longer.
-Fresh!
-Some delicious A-1, my pet?
-Oh, Roy, you shouldn't have.
[GULP]
-Hey, this is Polo.
-Hey, that's a reason to kiss.
-Oh, geez, kissing,
I love this stuff.
Love it.
-Hey, come on, it's the '60s.
There's no getting your fingers
through a woman's hair, there.
[HUMMING ALONG WITH SOUNDTRACK]
-The tender love theme.
-Uh oh.
Officer Interruptus.
-Again?
How many times do
you have to be told?
-12.
Heh heh.
-Have a heart, will ya?
-I do.
-Go chase that other couple.
-What other couple?
-Wanna handle this one, honey?
-Those idiots that went
deeper in the desert.
-Find them and chew
on them a while.
-We know that this
road goes nowhere.
So now, get.
No smart stuff.
We ain't trying to jump on ya.
Just get.
-We'll just go 10
yards up the road!
-The love vigilantes.
-It's the make out county line.
-Think we should try some
of that kissing, Burt?
No?
-Uh-uh.
-OK.
-They like kissing.
Go figure.
-Uh, want me to dri--
ok, I'll drive, I guess.
-Yup.
When there's a full
moon, I tell you,
that's when the crazies
come out, uh huh.
[IMITATES BUZZER]
-Uh, Stephanie, bring me
some coffee and a Pop Tart.
And bring your steno pad.
-Oh, man.
I gotta get ten more minutes.
[YAWNING]
-Wait a minute.
Do I smell bacon?
Honey, I love you!
-O, Manos.
Thou of primal darkness.
-It's a Moody Blues song.
-Thou who dwelleth in
the depth of the universe
in the black chasms of night.
-You know who you are.
-Come on, Satan.
Pick up.
I know you're there!
-Bill Buckner!
-Mm, now that is
a cute [INAUDIBLE]
-Oh my God, my
pants are on fire.
-"Manos-- the Hands of Fate"?
-Mm.
-"Manos."
-Thou bestoweth the Mother
Darkness upon thy faithful.
-Go ahead, I'm going to
put you on speaker phone.
-Thou doth make him
most blessed forever.
-Michael Franks!
-And thou who doth curse
with eternal burning thy
soul who transgress
against thee.
Holy art thou, holy art
-Yul Brynner!
-Holy art thou.
Manos' will be done.
-Mammy!
-Thy priesthood
remains steadfast--
-Aw, you can see the zipper.
-Remains constant.
Thy priesthood
remains righteous.
Thou has taught us, O
Manos, and we have listened.
Give ear to our words,
O Manos, and hear us.
Hear us!
-OK.
-For we are faithful.
And thou art our god.
-The black and
red Moses of soul.
-Arise, my wives--
-And iron my work shirt.
-Give ear to the words of Manos.
[SNORING]
-Arise, my wives, and
hear the will of Manos!
-OK, I'm up, I'm up!
[CHATTER]
-What was I thinking?
-I mean, who can afford
Lancome makeup, huh?
-One of these days, Alice!
-Alices.
-Women who lunch--
-And the Manos who love them.
Next Donahue.
-Why has the child
been brought here?
Why?
And a female child, at that.
-You can't just
buy the cleanser,
you have to buy
the whole package!
-I know, I know.
-You know, this scene is
strong enough for a Manos,
but made for a Woman-os.
I think.
-And now, back to,
"We Married Manos."
-I've never complained about
sacrificing a man, but a child?
-The woman is all we want.
The others must die!
They all must die!
We do not even want the woman!
-The child is a female.
She must not be destroyed.
She will grow up to be a woman.
-Oh, is that how that works?
-She must be killed!
-No!
-I am the oldest of the wives.
And it is my
privilege to say this.
-Enough!
Enough of this stupid bickering!
The child must die!
-Ohh, boo!
[BOOING]
-If you persist in
this foolishness--
-I'll take your charge cards!
Thank you, good night.
-Say what you will, I will
have no part of this madness.
-OK, Betty's out.
-And I say she must die!
-Boy, they're having a very
spirited group, tonight.
-Yeah.
-Torgo should never have
allowed them in and I want--
-You have caused enough trouble.
I think perhaps your service
to us is at its end, now.
Silence!
-Is golden!
-Silence!
-And now, my wives, I
shall deal with the one who
is responsible for
the child being here.
-But first, funnyman
Morty Gunty.
-Torgo, he's the one.
Get Torgo!
-You are responsible
for this nonsense.
We shall dispose of you later.
-What do I pay you
people for, anyway?
You're all just sitting around.
-It's a terrible mistake.
The man, yes.
The child, no.
-Cheese, maybe.
-Maybe she's right.
Maybe we should spare the child.
-And spoil the rod.
-It is against our
will that we stay here.
Do not make the child
die to satisfy him.
He does not need any more wives.
-I'm calling a cab.
Yes.
He has no more time
for us older wives.
[COUGHING]
-Hair is burning in there.
-Jealousy is not part of us.
Why are you so jealous of me?
[CAT FIGHT SOUNDS]
-You are a troublemaker.
You deserve to die!
-Next time, tell me when you're
wearing your white sheet!
-Die?
I may die.
But I do not care.
The child must live.
-Die, die, my darling.
-She's right!
We will not kill the child.
-But Manos would not approve.
-Just go over his head.
-The law of Manos
exists for us, only.
-Manos loves women.
She will grow up to be a woman.
But she must die!
-Let's hear Susan's
presentation,
and then let's break into
small groups and discuss this.
-Hey, and then you swing
your partners to and fro,
take her by the
arm and do-si-do!
Promenade.
-When the Master hears of
this, he will be furious.
-Yeah, you're lucky
my chick's here.
-You are all mad!
Mad, the whole lot of you!
The man, yes.
The child, no.
-Uhh-- Moms, I think
you might want to take
the kids out of the room, now.
-Yeah.
-Well, the talk's broke
down at this point.
-This is like the
Russian parliament.
-Next on ESPN-- full-contact
nightgown wrestling.
-"Designing Women,"
the lost episodes.
-And now.
The Manos Women's
Guild will re-enact
the Battle of Pearl Harbor.
-You know, this was the
alternate ending to "Beaches."
-I see London, I see France--
I see everybody's underpants!
-You know, this
isn't Lysistrata.
I like it, but it
-You know, after
this, they're gonna
laugh and cry and pierce
each other's ears.
-Yep.
-It's the Wilson
Phillips break up.
-Kinda wish this was
shirts versus skins.
-Heey!
-Heh heh heh.
-Hoo hoo, zing!
-(SINGING) Sometimes
it's hard to be a woman.
-You know what this
movie really needs?
It's Mark Singer.
-Oh yeah.
-I'm guessing this is the whole
reason this movie was made.
Right here.
-Pow!
-Boff!
Smack!
-Biff!
-Oh, great.
I never wanted to see this.
-And I don't want to see
Torgo in something sheer.
-No!
Torgo, you're missing the fight.
Get your dress on
and get in there!
-Torgo, you're the
laziest man on Mars.
-Torgo, get up.
You're late for your route.
-Ooh!
Right in the store.
-Ouch.
-Hey, boy.
-[PANTING]
-How ya doing?
Hey.
Sit.
-Thanks for letting me
crash here last night, man.
-Did my legs really
get big last night?
-Oh, man, he has
got a Torg-over.
-Don't help me or
anything, boss.
-This is so awkward.
-Do something!
God!
-What are you doing here?
-Keep away from me!
Keep away!
-You have failed us, Torgo.
I know of your
visits to the tomb.
-What happened to the
bright young Torgo I hired?
-My visits?
-The women have told me.
-Well, you parked
in the yellow zone.
-They may not be able to say
anything or move when you're
there, but they remember
everything you say to them.
-Oh, my God, I'm so embarrassed.
-And everything you do to them.
-Wha- what do you mean, boss?
-But Master, you have six wives.
Why can't I have one for myself?
-He makes a good point.
-You are not one of us.
Therefore you cannot
have one of them.
-Yes, but I have one now.
This one is mine!
You'll never get her.
-You have failed us, Torgo.
For this, you must die.
-Ooh, really strict boss, huh?
-Wow.
-Failed you?
No.
You have failed yourselves!
You never killed them!
I'll help them!
-You have failed
and you must die!
-You can't kill me, I quit.
-I'm-- going to have to ask
for my last paycheck right now,
sir.
-What?
What?
Uh.
Oh.
-Is this your card?
-You know, as a boss, he should
be building them up right now.
-Does this bug you?
Does this bug you?
I'm not touching you.
-Cut it out, man.
-So he kills him by waving a
rusty tailpipe in front of him?
-Get that cat off the piano.
-Oh, I'm just kidding, Torgo,
I'm not going to kill you.
Get back to work, ya bum.
-I just remembered Family
Circus was really funny today.
-Manos.
God of primal darkness.
-Can you believe this?
-As thou hast decreed,
so have I done.
The hands of fate
have doomed this man.
-You know what?
I bet Torgo's
changing back there.
-Oh.
Hey-y--
-(SINGING) Never steal
anything we-- huh?
Say, who's the new guy?
-Hey, who planted a man?
-Oh, I see you're kind
of tied up right now.
Ha ha, I'm dead,
but I'm still funny.
-Oh, I hope she doesn't make
like Jenny Fields, oh ho.
-No, I shouldn't, I--
-(SINGING) I don't
know how to love him!
[FART SOUNDS]
-Let's see.
Honey, I was tied
up and unconscious.
There was nothing I could do!
-Is she telling him a secret?
-Mhm.
-All over him.
-Huh, I have the feeling
you're not interested in me.
-Don't you ever try that again!
Ever!
-It was a brief affair.
And it ended bitterly.
-Oh, I'm sorry, I thought
you were someone else.
-Uh, where was I?
Oh yeah, back to the supply hut.
-We return to "Girl Talk"
with Virginia Graham.
-Relax, it's a
natural exfoliant.
Just ease into it.
-Say uncle!
-(MUFFLED) Uncle!
-The women are fighting!
-Aw, again?
-When are you going
to kill me, boss?
-And the bench is clear!
-It's a rather gentle rumble.
-She's my sister!
She's my daughter!
She's my sister!
-Movie has kind of a Ken
Russell feel to it, I'd say.
-Carol Brady?
-The Maidenform woman.
You never know where
she'll turn up.
-Look, I think we were basically
all in agreement anyways.
-These clearance
sales are brutal.
[SNORING]
-Huh?
Big knees!
Oh!
Oh.
-Hey, how come no one
invited me to the brawl?
-Michael?
Michael, where are you?
[HUMMING]
-Oh, I don't like
that neckline at all.
Oh now, say, this is cute.
-Salutations, imperfect one!
I am the Master, and you are
mysteriously drawn to me!
[SNICKER]
-Everything I say, you
must do right away,
without having to ask twice!
I am evil!
And mean!
And unforgiving!
In your brokenness you have
failed, and now must repent.
Bow down now before me!
Bow down!
-Oh, hi, Joel.
[RESUMES HUMMING]
-Oh, come on, Tom.
I was just commanding
you to do my will.
Besides, look-- (SHOUTING)
come to me, for I am the magnet
and you are steel!
-Well you look like Maude.
-Well, come on, I think
this cloak exudes power
and manliness.
And, uh, hey look, I got
a horrifying hell beast
right here.
[PANTING]
-That's pretty scary.
-You just look like
Maude with a hell beast.
-Oh, you mean Estelle Getty?
But Tom, look!
-Come on, Joel.
The cloak is grand, the
workmanship is superb,
but a neat caftan
doesn't automatically
qualify you as the
Devil's spin doctor.
-Oh, come on, look, it's lined.
I got inside pockets, I
got a little special one
for my Mentos.
It's even got a cotton panel.
-Ah, Joel, uh-- Tom's right.
It's just not working.
You're not the evil type.
-What do you mean?
-Well, for one thing, your,
your face is too friendly.
Second, your eyebrows,
they arc softly as
opposed to jutting inward.
And well, frankly, Joel, you
blush in the most adorable way.
-This is really embarrassing
Oh great, the Mads are calling.
-Uh, hi, fellas.
Look, I, uh, I, I
just wanted to let
you know, I know this
movie's a tough one
and I just wanted to let
you know, I feel for ya.
-Doctor?
Caramel corn's ready.
Do you want it in your
"Little Mermaid" bowl?
-Uh-- fine!
Sure.
Now you realize if you
tell Frank I've done this,
I'll have to kill him.
So let's not, OK?
Enough said?
All righty?
Buh-bye.
-It's cute, though.
-Ah, come on.
-Oh, please, God.
Where's Mike?
-Freddie Mercury!
-Jimmy Hoffa.
The last known photo.
-More of the same.
-Girls, girls,
you're all pretty!
Stop!
What foolishness is this?
-There!
-Manos must be served!
-There you are.
-I've served!
-She is the one.
She has upset all of our plans.
-This foolishness must stop!
-OK!
-(SINGING) All my bags are
packed, I'm ready to go.
I'm--
-Uh, uh, boss, I really need
to know about the execution.
Uh, have things--
-Wow, I used to go out
with all of these women
and now they're all
here, Kodachrome.
-Well, we're going to
do some story time now.
Torgo, sit down.
-There's been enough trouble.
-Right here in River City.
-Our purpose must be served.
There will be no
further insolence.
-But I need my insulin.
-But the child!
-We cannot kill a child!
-Yes we can!
-Let's wrestle for it!
-You have caused enough trouble.
-Well, Cindy started it.
-No, I didn't.
-When we've disposed of Torgo,
we shall take care of you!
-Um, should Torgo
be at this meeting?
-Your power failed you.
-You know what
she's really saying.
-Seize her!
And prepare her for sacrifice!
-Well, I guess I'm just
a little too outspoken.
-The Amazing Tecnicolor Poncho.
-All right, now let's see, the
rabbit comes out of the hole,
goes around the
tree, that's it, OK.
-Now, remember, I like
to be lightly braised.
-Well done, my wives.
-Now, get the potatoes.
-The will of Manos
shall be served.
-Pull my finger!
-We are going to make
you look terrific.
-They're going to
wax his bikini area.
-He's got Earl Campbell thighs.
-Ohh.
Oof.
Oh, boy I'm exhausted.
Oh, my dogs are barking
today, let me tell you.
-Torgo, heh, that guy
can sleep anywhere.
-It is the will of Manos
that he be sacrificed.
-Oh, no.
Not liturgical dance.
-Hey!
Is he flipping us off?
-Kill.
Kill.
Kill!
-OK.
-Manos has decreed it.
Kill!
-Yes, dear.
I'm doing it, dear.
-Boy, would I wouldn't give
to be Torgo, right now.
-Look, I'm just a temp,
I really don't, uh--
-They're rolfing him to death.
-Does this make you cry?
Huh, baby?
Cry?
You gonna cry, huh?
-Mike!
Help us!
-You have to want
to help yourself.
-Oh, uh, this has been
a good night, honey.
Uh, uh, honey?
Honey?
-Mm, you know, I love
my Craftmatic Pole.
That was the most comfortable
sleep I've ever had.
-Oh, whoa.
Gotta go, gotta go, gotta go.
-Hey, Dear Eveready, I was
tied to a post all night
and left my flashlight on.
But the batteries--
-Don't play with your food.
-There!
Ha ha hah!
-Oh, wow.
-Oh, come on, die.
My arms are getting tired.
-Uh, Beth, do you
want to help out here?
Hmm?
-Whoops.
-You know, there are
certain flaws in this film.
-Margaret?
Open the door!
-I can't, I'm waiting for Mike!
-Margaret!
Open the door!
-No, I don't like you anymore!
[GRUNTS]
-Hey!
-Enough!
The ceremony is done.
-[INAUDIBLE] and punch
the fellowship hall.
-Uh, can I have the watermelons
that are in his pants?
-Oh, now.
You know, Torgo doesn't get
a lot of respect around here.
-Oh, great.
Where am I going to
find another Torgo?
-Hey.
(SINGING) Smoke on the weirdo.
[LAUGHTER]
-Come here.
-The new Pope has
not been chosen.
-Ugh.
Boss, you wanna give
me a hand, here?
I'm having a little
gravity problem.
-Wow, you know the hand
thing really works.
I gotta try it with
women next time.
-This is the tender side of
"Manos-- The Hands of Fate."
-Oh, this is gonna be just
like in "The Grifters."
Only worse.
[DIABOLICAL LAUGHTER]
-(SINGING) Charred finger!
-Thanks, boss.
I'm off.
Buh-bye.
-Uh, the Jamaican
wings are ready.
[LAUGHTER CONTINUES]
-This doesn't really strike
me as a "ha ha" kind of funny.
-It's more of a
quiet kind of funny.
-Yeah, introspective.
[LAUGHING,_STILL]
-I'm hungry.
-Killing doesn't help anymore.
You're all finished!
-Hey!
I ordered it medium-rare!
-Your time will come as soon as
we have disposed of the others!
Go find the others!
Hurry!
Before the night gets away!
-That's a guy's hand, not a
sparkler, for crying out loud.
[LAUGHING RESUMES]
-I think he has the most
musical laugh I've heard.
-Light hand and get away.
-At the window.
I saw him at that window.
-OK, honey.
We'll leave, we'll leave.
-Put some clothes on.
-Now!
I can't stand it any longer.
Please, Mike.
-We really haven't given
this hotel a chance.
-We'll hide in the desert.
Someone will help.
-The gods will destroy you.
Your power failed!
-Oh, she's reading him
the Riot Act, huh boy?
Let me tell ya.
-Oh, right into a cow pie!
-Aw, man.
[SOBBING]
-Uh, honey, we should
really get going.
-Did Mommy come back
from another bar?
-I can't take it, Mike!
I can't make it!
-OK, honey, we'll
meet you there, then.
Bye.
-Save baby!
Save Debbie!
-A most dangerous game.
-You guys, come on!
You're ruining the sacrifice.
Guys.
-Heh, it's Mary Kay-KK.
-Julia Roberts?
-Seen it!
-I wish those hands
would just push him over.
-So, they're, um-- looking.
-Mhm.
-So, "Manos--"
-"The Hands of Fate."
-Yes, exactly.
-No, Maggie.
We can make it.
We'll rest here for a minute.
-Daddy, I'm sitting
in poison ivy.
-They'll never think of
looking for us at the house.
-You know, you might
have a point there.
-Please, Mike.
Please, I can't go any farther!
-Listen, we can lock
ourselve in the kitchen.
I have my gun.
-What--?
Honey, I'm brilliant.
You could kiss me!
-OK.
I'm outta here.
-You tampered in God's domain.
-We'll have to go back.
-OK.
-So I'm am idiot.
-It might be the safest
place, especially
since they're out
here looking for us.
-Daddy, I'm scared.
Where's my puppy?
Please, Debbie.
Not now.
-Your puppy's compost, kid.
-(IRISH ACCENT) All
right, break it up.
Nothing to-- ah, forget it.
-Hey, uh, is somebody
filming a bad movie out here?
-These guys have
the longest shift.
-Oh!
There you are, Ted.
Didn't see you over there.
-I'd like to dedicate this
next song to the little lady.
-That sure sounded like shots.
We'd better check.
-This hour of the night?
There can't be anybody out here.
This is the boondocks.
-Well, sound does travel
a long way at night.
It could be clear over in
Mexico, for that matter.
-Or even Europe.
Parts of Canada.
-Maybe we didn't hear it.
Ever think of that?
-Well, uh, you know what?
I'm-- I'm not all that curious.
Let's go get some
hash browns, huh?
-Creamsicle?
-Phew!
I'm bushed after that.
-Red, ever feel like crying
and you just don't know why?
-You know, the
place looks pretty
cheerful without those
devil worshippers around.
-Sheesh, it's like
they're walking
into a John Waters film.
-Surprise, surprise, surprise!
[PANTING SOUNDS]
-Hey, Russ Weatherwax really
topped himself with this dog.
-Can-- can you hold
that cue card up?
Um-- what's that say?
Oh yeah.
Arf!
-(SINGING) At Beneficial.
-Focus.
F- oh, it's a stare down.
Focus.
-Oh, thank you very much.
A shot in the face, how nice.
-Focus.
-Meanwhile in Toledo.
-Uh, no, wait a minute.
Did this movie just lap itself?
[THUNDER]
-(SINGING) Riders on the storm--
-Another convertible,
another town, another movie?
-"Manos-- The Hands of Fate"
-Sure is good to get away.
Damn the rain.
-Vacations are fine, but
this one should be great.
-Yeah, the gang's coming up
for the weekend, what a blast!
-What a blast!
[HICCUP]
-Hmm.
-Wha?
Oh, wait, there's
something gaining on us.
Uh, oh-- never mind
it just the top.
I'm intensely stupid.
-Just take your half of the
road out of the middle, there.
That's right.
-This must be a weekly series.
-So, so I told Gary that I
was going on this vacation.
So he goes, well,
then, I'm going
hunting with Jeff next weekend.
Well, that's when
we were at Knives.
And then Lou sang
"Fernando" and then
Gary-- oh he sings so good.
Oh, you should meet
Jeff some time.
Do you like Barry Manilow songs?
I know the farmers
need rain, but when
it's damp like this my hair just
explodes, just ex-puh looodes.
Ooh, ooh, I'm
feeling kinda gassy,
McNuggets, you know
they make me so gassy,
all that grease and all.
It really helps if you
drink eight to ten glasses
of water a day.
Did you know that?
Sometimes I drink
five, sometimes
I drink nine just to make up for
the other three I didn't drink.
Coffee and diet
drinks don't count e--
You know, this is pretty
country, isn't it?
You know, it's really kind
of a blessing in disguise
that I didn't get
accepted to college, eh?
You know, I'm gonna have
to revise my 20 year plan,
but-- oh, did I tell you
about my 20 year plan?
OK, well, OK, listen here.
In year one, this
is the year when
I'm going to take off
those extra seven pounds.
You know, that's equal to
seven pounds of butter, he he,
so it's like I'm wearing
seven pounds of butter!
Hah, and, uh, now--
oh, oh, where was I?
Oh, oh yeah, so my
aunt and uncle here,
they celebrated their
20th anniversary,
and my uncle wanted to
sing, uh, "Sunrise, Sunset."
He wanted me to sing
that, and I haven't
sung that since Cindy's
wedding, and well, she never
thanked me for that.
Well, I'm, still-- uh,
well, she, you know,
she's probably really
busy and all, with--
-Still kissing.
Six straight days?
[THUNDER]
-A strange sounding door.
-Joan Kennedy?
-Welcome.
-The hell?
-Whoa.
This is blowing my mind.
-Oh, man.
-No!
[BOOING]
-Where's Torgo?
We came to see Torgo.
-I am Michael.
I take care of the place
while the Master is away.
[ANNOYED GRUNT]
-Oh, it's over.
[RELIEVED SIGHS]
-I ain't gonna play Sun City.
-He has a kind face.
-It's starting over!
-No, no, no!
I can't take any--
-This really "bites."
-Titles by Keith Haring.
-This limited edition
suitable for framing print
is now on sale in lobby.
Along with the soundtrack to,
"Manos-- the Hands of Fate."
-Starring-- no one!
-(SINGING) Faded photographs.
-Which do you find
the most loathsome?
-Oh, Joel, there's a buffet of
loathsomeness in this movie.
-Do you think he was
proud of this role?
-Remember that, the
leaning scene, there?
-Yeah, heh, he went on to
do Torgo at Disney World.
-This was a heartwarming scene.
-Ben Vereen?
Why is he yelling at us?
-Ah, forget it.
-Jerk!
Ew.
-She was traumatized
for life after this.
-I bet.
-Oh, now this one.
She was good.
She was the glue that held
this picture together.
-No, I don't want
to be in this movie!
-They all wanted to be
Dean Martin's gold diggers,
you know.
-Make out, come on!
-Kiss her!
-(SINGING) Sing
around the campfire--
-And you know, these
are all outtakes.
This is the stuff
they didn't use.
-[INAUDIBLE] film.
-Crew?
They had a crew?
I do not believe they had a--
-OK, whoa, everybody pick out
someone you want to punch.
-Where to start?
-Touch it.
Touch it, come on!
You want to.
-Oh, ho, and these two.
Like Allen and Rossi.
They were really--
they stole the show.
-Oh, they must be
dental technicians.
-Oh, look at that cavity.
Have you been flossing?
-Oh and who can forget
the nutty sorority rush?
-And the tender
"peeping Torgo" scene.
-A triple boo for Warren.
-If you'd like to
contact Harold P. Warren,
look in the Yellow Pages for
the Fertilizer Corporation
of Texas.
-The End?
Yes.
No!
I want to change my answer.
-Now I'll always wonder.
-Come on!
-Let's go.
-OK, thank you, El Paso.
Good night, we're outta here!
-Woo!
-We're going to
take a break, we've
been "Manos-- the
Hands of Fate."
[GYPSY IMITATING FIGHT MUSIC]
-Crow, I still don't see how
dressing in diaphanous robes
and slapping each other around
is gonna make Joel happy.
-Well, don't hurt yourself
thinking about it.
Now shut up and
wrestle, spinach chin!
-Hey, hey, what the sam scrach
is going on around here?
-Uh, uh, well we're just playing
the Satan lady wrestling game.
Thought we'd cheer you up.
-Guys!
Gypsy!
I don't think this is
a good idea for you.
-Why?
We're wearing ear protection.
--I'll explain later.
What do you think, sirs?
Gypsy!
-Oh.
That's great, Joel.
Very amusing, uh.
Oh, by the way, did you
see Andy Capp today?
Heh, very funny.
Hehe, he came home after
being drunk all night and--
-Frank!
-Cheating on Flo--
-Where is our pizza?
It's been two hours
since you ordered!
-Well, I called Togo's Pizza.
They were busy, so
I ended up having
to order from Torgo's Pizza.
[DOORBELL]
-Come in!
-Large sausage and
mushroom thin crust?
-That's us.
-The total is $14.50, please.
-Here.
-Do you have anything smaller?
I only carry $20 in change.
-That's all I have.
-I have a $20.
-Well, why didn't you
give him the $20??
-I was saving it,
you know, for that--
-Would you please
give him the $20?
-OK, just-- Oh.
-Well, thank you,
I'll get your change.
-Oh, keep it.
-Thank you very much, sir.
Let me get your
complimentary crazy bread.
-No!
No!
No, that's OK!
-That's quite all right.
Hey, what about our pop?
-I left it in the car.
I'll be right back.
[GROANS]
-Until next time, Joel.
Push the button, Frank.
-Say, you know,
it's been two hours,
but it's still pretty warm!
-They always do that.
-Why don't you guys
leave us alone?